Local 1199 Oral History Project 5680 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Doris Turner: 11/23/1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Doris Turner: 10/26/1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Doris Turner: 11/23/1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Doris Turner: 10/26/1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Doris Turner: 11/23/1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Doris Turner: 10/28/1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Cornelius Volk: 7/15/1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Cornelius Volk: 7/15/1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Kay Tillow (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Kay Tillow: 10/21/1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Kay Tillow: 10/21/1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Charles Balancia: 3/2/1976 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Charles Balancia: 3/2/1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Martin Cherkosky: 4/8/1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Martin Cherkosky: 4/8/1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Cherkosky: 4/8/1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- James Fitzpatric: 7/11/1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- James Fitzpatric: 7/11/1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Sarah Goldstein: 1/16/1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Sarah Goldstein: 1/16/1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Victor Weingarten: 2/6/1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Victor Weingarten: 2/6/1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Victor Weingarten: 2/6/1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Diane Bianculli (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Diane Bianculli (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Diane Bianculli II (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Sy Broomer: 3/31/1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Clifton Burgess: 7/29/1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Ida Cameron: 4/25/1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Id Cameron: 4/25/1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Cassie Cosby: 3/23/1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Cassie Cosby: 3/23/1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Andrew Danielli (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Andrew Danielli (Box 19, Folder 2)
- David Aberdeen: 11/8/1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- David Aberdeen: 11/18/1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- David Aberdeen: 11/8/1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Edward DeMarco: 8/1/1977 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  tape 1/side 1 only
- Marshall Dubin: 12/3/1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Marshall Dubin: 12/3/1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Marshall Dubin: 12/3/1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Marshall Dubin: 3/25/1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Marshall Dubin: 3/25/1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Marshall Dubin: 3/25/1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Marshall Dubin: 11/12/1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Marshall Dubin: 11/12/1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Harry Epstein (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Harry Epstein (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Mae Harrison: 7/13/1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Telbert King: 12/20/1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Telbert King: 12/20/1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Arthur Landsberg: 7/18/1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Jesse Olson: 4/12/1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Jess Olson: 4/17/1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  tape 1/side 1 of 3
- Jesse Olson: 4/17/1985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  tape 1/side 2 of 3
- Jesse Olson: 4/17/1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  tape 1/3 of 3
- The Public's Health WFUV (Box 21, Folder 6)
- The Public Health WFUV (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Irving Goffshagen: 11/16/1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Irving Goffshagen: 1/16/1976 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Emerido Cruz: 11/12/1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Emerido Cruz: 11/12/1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Emerido Cruz: 11/12/1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  side 3 (A side only)
- Leon Davis: 1/16/1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  tape 3/side 2
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  tape III/side 1 only
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  tape II/side 2
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  tape II/side 1
- Leon Davis: 1/5/1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  tape 2/side A only
- Leon Davis: 4/1/1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Leon Davis: 4/1/1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Leon Davis: 1/16/1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Leon Davis: 1/6/1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  tape 4/side 1
- Leon Davis: 1/6/1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  tape 4/side 2
- Leon Davis: 1/5/1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Leon Davis: 1/5/1976 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Leon Davis at Thatchell Dinner 1199 #Q: 9/16/1977 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Hilda Jogin: 6/30/1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Hilda Jogin: 6/30/1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Phil Kamenkowitz I: 11/29/1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Kamenkowitz II (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Phil Kamenkowitz I: 11/29/1976 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Kamenkowitz II (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Eddie Kay: 7/29/1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Eddie Kay: 7/29/1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Bill Michaelson (Box 24, Folder 9)
  tape II/side 1 only
- Bill Michaelson: 6/22/1977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Bill Michaelson: 6/22/1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Bob Muehlen Kamp: 12/10/1976 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Bob Muehlen Kamp: 12/10/1976 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Taylor II (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Taylor II (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Harry Van Arsdale: 9/7/1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Harry Van Arsdale: 9/7/1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Harry Van Arsdale: 9/1/1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  tape 1/side A
- Harry Van Arsdale: 9/1/1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Marie Barkum: 4/4/1977 -- interview 2 (Box 33)
- I. Bennett: interview 3 (Box 34)
- Sinai Barker: interview 6 (Box 35)
- John Connorton: interview 10 (Box 36)
- Cormack / Beth Israel: interview 13a (Box 37)
- Cormack / Beth Israel: interview 13b (Box 38)
- Davis: interview 15 (Box 39)
- Davis: interview 16 (Box 40)
- Davis: interview 17/18 (Box 41)
- Leon Davis: interview 19 (Box 42)
- Marshall Dubin: interview 21 (Box 43)
- Marshall Dubin: interview 21b (Box 44)
- Rev. Thomas Duffy: 2/28/1980 -- interview 22 (Box 45)
- Elliot Godoff and Lillian Godoff: 11/12/1976 -- interview 30a (Box 46)
- Lillian Godoff: interview 30b (Box 47)
- Rev. Henry Grant: 2/27/1980 -- interview 32 (Box 48)
- Howard Lichtenstein: 6/26/1977 -- interview 35a (Box 49)
- Lichtenstein: interview 35b (Box 50)
- David Kaufman: 5/26/1977 -- interview 37a (Box 51)
- David Kaufman: interview 37b (Box 52)
- Kosloski: interview 39a (Box 53)
- Kosloski: interview 39b (Box 54)
- Norman Metzger: 4/18/1977 -- interview 41a (Box 55)
- Norman Metzger: 4/29/1977 -- interview 41b (Box 56)
- Norman Metzger: 4/28/1977 -- interview 41c (Box 57)
- Ted Mitchell: 3/16/1976 -- interview 43a (Box 58)
- Todd Mitchell: 11/24/1975 -- interview 43 b (Box 59)
- Ted Mitchell: interview 44a (Box 60)
- Mitchell: 11/24/1975 -- interview 44b (Box 61)
- Morris Katz: interview 45 (Box 62)
- Mary Moultrio: 2/28/1980 -- interview 46 (Box 63)
- Julio Pagan: interview 50a (Box 64)
- Julio Pagan: 4/20/1977 -- interview 50b (Box 65)
- A. H. Raskin: 6/15/1977 -- interview 51 (Box 66)
- Karl Roth: 11/3/1976 -- interview 55a (Box 67)
- Roth: 11/3/1976 -- interview 55b (Box 68)
- Eddie Sanchez: 3/23/1977 -- interview 57 (Box 69)
- Wm Saunders: 3/1/1980 -- interview 58a (Box 70)
- William Saunders: 3/1/1980 -- interview 58b (Box 71)
- Cecil Sheps: 7/12/1979 -- interview 60a (Box 72)
- Cecil Sheps: 7/12/1979 -- interview 60b (Box 73)
- Judge Simuton's: interview 61 (Box 74)
- Dr. Martin Steinberg: interview 62 (Box 75)
- Dr. Martin Steinberg: interview 63 (Box 76)
- Bill Taylor: 12/15/1976 -- interview 65a (Box 77)
- Taylor: interview 65b (Box 78)
- Elon Tompkins: 3/23/1977 -- interview 67 (Box 79)
- Dave White: 6/5/1979 -- interview 72a (Box 80)
- Dave White: 6/5/1979 -- interview 72b (Box 81)
- John E. Wise: 2/28/1980 -- interview 73 (Box 82)
- Lucille Works / Beth Israel: interview 74 (Box 83)
- Andrew Young: interview 75 (Box 84)
- Gloria Arana: 3/31/1977 (Box 85)
  interview not labeled
- Gloria Arana: 4/25/1977 (Box 86)
- Birnbaum Boxwell (Box 87)
- Birnbaum Boswell (Box 88)
- Moe Foner: 3/9/1977 (Box 89)
  interview not numbered
- Fritz Field (Box 90)
- Edith Garcia (Box 91)
- Marjorie Phillips: 7/1/1977 (Box 93)
  interview tape not numbered
- Methodist Hospital: 7/8/1976 (Box 94)
- Gloria Arana: 2/23/1977 (Box 92)
- Nellie Morris: 1/8/1976 (Box 95)
- Ted Mitchell: 9/28/1977 - at retirement dinner (Box 96)
- Ramon Malave - 12/6/1976 (Box 97)
  tape 1
- Ramon Malave: 12/6/1976 (Box 98)
  tape 2
- Grace Glassberg: 3/23/1977 - Mt. Sinai (Box 99)
- Henry Nicholas: 1/11/1978 (Box 100)
- Henry Nicholas 4/14/1982 (Box 101)
- Henry Nicholas: 1/11/1978 (Box 102)
- Henry Nicholas (Box 103)
  tape 3
- Moe Foner interview: 7/1/1977 (Box 104)
- Moe Foner: 7/22/1975 (Box 105)
- M. Foner: 7/22/1975 (Box 106)
- Moe Foner: 4/1/1976 (Box 107)
- Moe Foner: 4/1/1976 (Box 108)
- Moe Foner: 7/1/1977 (Box 109)
- Moe Foner 2 (Box 110)
- Foner 3 (Box 111)
- Moe Foner: 12/22/1975 (Box 112)
- Moe Foner: 10/26/1976 (Box 113)
- Claude Ferrara: 3/16/1976 (Box 114)
- Claude Ferrara (Box 115)
- G. Cooper: 12/19/1975 (Box 116)
- Grosvenor Cooper: 12/19/1975 (Box 117)
- Jim Bryant: 3/23/1977 (Box 118)
- Joseph Brown: 11/12/1975 (Box 119)
- I-Kon Downs (Box 120)
- SPL Connor: 12/15/1975 (Box 121)
- Morris Hodara (Box 122)
- Hodara (Box 123)
- Ken Downs (Box 124)
- Joseph Brown (Box 125)
- Thelma Bowles: 2/18/1977 (Box 126)
- Thelma Bowles: 12/3/1975 (Box 127)
- Thelma Bowles: 12/3/1975 (Box 128)
- Ernestine Bowen (Box 129)
- Ernestine Bowen - Mt. Sinai: 3/23/1977 (Box 130)
- Andrew Danielli (Box 131)
- Diane Bianculli (Box 132)
- Diane Bianculli (Box 133)
- Sarah Goldstein: 1/16/1976 (Box 134)
- Jas. Fitzpatrick: 7/11/1977 (Box 135)
- Charles Balancia: 3/2/1976 (Box 136)
- Aberdeen David: 11/8/1976 (Box 137)
- Aberdeen David: 11/8/1976 (Box 138)
- Victor Weingarten: 2/6/1976 (Box 139)
- Victor Weingarten: 2/6/1976 (Box 140)
- Cassie Cosby: 3/23/1977 (Box 141)
- Ida Cameron - Mt. Sinai: 4/25/1977 (Box 142)
- Burgoss (Box 143)
- Sy Broomor: 3/31/1977 (Box 144)
- Henry Melida: 4/12/1985 (Box 145)
- Irving Stern: 1/16/1976 (Box 146)
- Cornelius Bell Volk: Beth Israel -- 7/15/1977 (Box 147)
- Arguilla Ortiz: 7/11/1977 (Box 148)
- Mary Riley: 7/6/1977 (Box 149)
- Bayard Rustin: 6/20/1977 (Box 150)
- Doris Turner: 11/23/1976 (Box 151)
- Turner: 10/28/1976 (Box 152)
- Kay Tillow: 10/21/1980 (Box 153)
- Kay Tillow: 10/21/1980 (Box 154)
- Sam Schmuckler: 4/4/1977 (Box 155)
- Sam Schmuckler: 4/4/1977 (Box 156)
- Doris Turner: 10/26/1976 (Box 157)
- Turner: 11/23/1976 (Box 158)
- Mildred Reeves (Box 159)
- Mildred Reeves (Box 160)
- martin Cherkasky: 4/8/1976 (Box 161)
- Dr. Cherkosky: 4/8/1976 (Box 162)
- Betty Rosoff: 12/8/1975 (Box 163)
- Betty Rosoff (Box 164)
- Henry Nicholas: 4/14/1982 (Box 165)
- Nicholas tape: 10/14/1988 (Box 166)
- Bill Michaelson (Box 167)
  tape II
- Harry Van Arsdale: 9/1/1977 (Box 168)
- Harry Van Arsdale: 9/7/1977 (Box 169)
- Bill Michaelson: 6/22/1977 (Box 170)
- Bob Muehlenkamp: 12/18/1976 (Box 171)
- Dubin (Box 172)
- Marshall Dubin: 11/12/1975 (Box 173)
- Dubin pt. II: 12/3/1975 (Box 174)
- Interview - Emerido Cruz: 11/12/1975 (Box 175)
- Interview - Emerido Cruz: 11/12/1975 (Box 176)
- Theo Davis: 1/5/1976 (Box 177)
- Leon Davis: 1/5/1976 (Box 178)
- Leon Davis: 1/6/1976 (Box 179)
- Leon Davis: 1/6/1976 (Box 180)
  tape 4
- Leon Davis: 4/1/1976 (Box 181)
  tape I
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 182)
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 183)
  tape III
- Marshall Rubin: 3/25/1976 (Box 184)
- Marshall Dubin: 3/25/1976 (Box 185)
- Jesse Olson: 4/17/1985 (Box 186)
- Jess Olson: 4/17/1985 (Box 187)
- Harry Epstein: 3/7/1977 (Box 188)
- Epstein 2 (Box 189)
- Phil Kamenkowitz: 11/29/1976 (Box 190)
- Kamenkowitz II (Box 191)
- Interview with Arthur Landsberg: 7/8/1977 (Box 192)
- Telbert King: 12/20/1982 (Box 193)
- Taylor II (Box 194)
- Edward Demarco: 8/1/1977 (Box 195)
- The Public's Health: 9/5/1989 (Box 196)
- Eddie Kay: 7/29/1977 (Box 197)
- Irving Goffshagen: 1/16/1976 (Box 198)
- Mae Harrison: 7/13/1977 (Box 199)
- Hilda Joquin: 6/30/1977 (Box 200)
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 201)
- Leon Davis: 9/16/1977 (Box 202)
- Moe Foner: 4/1/1976 (Box 203)
- Moe Foner: 4/1/1976 (Box 204)
- Moe Foner: 7/1/1977 -- 7/1/1976 (Box 205)
- Moe Foner: 7/1/1977 (Box 206)
  side 1 & 2
- Moe Foner: 7/22/1975 (Box 207)
- Moe Foner: 7/22/1975 (Box 208)
- Moe Foner: 12/23/1975 (Box 209)
- Moe Foner: 12/23/1975 (Box 210)
- Moe Foner: 12/23/1975 (Box 211)
- Moe Foner: 10/26/1976 (Box 212)
- Grace Glassberg: 3/23/1977 (Box 213)
- Claude Ferrara: 3/16/1976 (Box 214)
- Claude Ferrara (Box 215)
- Morris Hodara (Box 216)
- Hodara 2 (Box 217)
- Ernestine Bowen: 3/23/1977 (Box 218)
- Ernestine Bowen: 3/23/1977 (Box 219)
- Sal Cordes: 12/15/1975 (Box 220)
- Joseph Brown: 11/12/1975 (Box 221)
- Joseph Brown (Box 222)
- Jim Bryant: 3/23/1977 (Box 223)
- Thelma Bowles: 12/3/1979 (Box 224)
- Thelma Bowles: 12/3/1975 (Box 225)
- Thelma Bowles: 12/18/1977 (Box 226)
- Ken Downs (Box 227)
- Ken Downs (Box 228)
- Grosevnor Cooper: 12/19/1975 (Box 229)
- G. Cooper: 12/19/1975 (Box 230)
- Bob Muchlenkamp: 12/10/1976 (Box 232)
  copy
- Emerido Cruz: 11/12/1975 (Box 233)
- Emirido Cruz: 11/12/1975 (Box 234)
  side A only / copy
- Leon Davis: 4/1/1976 (Box 235)
- Leon Davis: 1/6/1976 (Box 236)
  tape 4/copy
- Leon Davis at Thatchell Dinner: 9/16/1977 (Box 237)
- Ted Mitchell: 9/28/1977 (Box 238)
- Ramon Malave: 12/6/1976 (Box 239)
- Ramon Malave (Box 240)
- henry Nicholas: 1/11/1978 (Box 241)
- Henry Nicholas: 1/11/1978 (Box 242)
- Henry Nicholas: 4/12/1985 (Box 243)
- Henry Nicholas: 10/14/1988 (Box 244)
- Henry Nicholas: 4/14/1982 (Box 245)
- Henry Nicholas: 4/14/1982 (Box 246)
- Nellie Morris: 1/8/1976 (Box 247)
- Mildren Reeves (Box 248)
- Mildren Reeves (Box 249)
- Cornelius 'Bell' Volk: 7/15/1977 (Box 250)
- Sam Schmuckler: 4/4/1977 (Box 251)
- Sam Schmuckler: 4/4/1977 (Box 252)
- Irving Stern: 1/16/1976 (Box 253)
- Kay Tillow: 10/21/1980 (Box 254)
- Kay Tillow: 10/21/1980 (Box 255)
- Doris Turner: 10/26/1976 (Box 256)
- Doris Turner: 10/26/1976 (Box 257)
- Doris Turner: 11/23/1976 (Box 258)
- Doris Turner: 11/23/1976 (Box 259)
- Bayard Rustin: 6/2/1977 (Box 260)
- Betty Rosoff: 12/8/1975 (Box 261)
- Betty Rosoff #2: 12/8/1975 (Box 262)
- Arguilla Ortiz: 7/11/1977 (Box 263)
- Mary Riley: 7/6/1977 (Box 264)
- Bill Michaelson: 6/22/1977 (Box 265)
  tape II/copy
- Eddie Kay: 7/29/1977 (Box 266)
- Leon Davis: 1/5/1976 (Box 267)
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 268)
- Leon Davis: 7/27/1977 (Box 269)
  tape III/copy
- Leon Davis: 1/16/1976 (Box 270)
  tape 3 / copy
- Harry Van Arsdale: 9/1/1977 (Box 271)
  tape 1/copy
- Taylor II (Box 272)
- Sarah Goldstein: 1/16/1976 (Box 273)
- Dr. Cherkosky: 4/8/1976 (Box 274)
- Charles Balancia: 3/2/1976 (Box 275)
- David Aberdeen: 11/8/1976 (Box 276)
- David Aberdeen: 11/8/1976 (Box 277)
- Mae Harrison: 7/13/1977 (Box 278)
- Clifford Burgess: 7/29/1977 (Box 279)
- Arthur Landesberg: 7/8/1977 (Box 280)
- Dr. Martin Cherkosky: 4/8/1976 (Box 281)
- Elbert King: 12/20/1982 (Box 282)
- James Fitzpatrick: 7/11/1977 (Box 283)
- Andrew Daniel's (Box 284)
- Ed DeMarco: 8/1/1977 (Box 285)
- Victor Weingarten: 2/6/1976 (Box 286)
- Victor Weingarten: 2/6/1976 (Box 287)
- Epstein (Box 287)
- Ida Cameron: 4/25/1977 (Box 288)
- Cassie Cosby: 3/23/1975 (Box 289)
- Sy Broomer: 3/31/1977 (Box 290)
- Jess Olson: 4/12/1985 (Box 291)
- Marshall Dubin: 11/12/1975 (Box 292)
- Marshall Dubin: 12/3/1975 (Box 293)
- Marshall Dubin: 12/3/1975 (Box 294)
- Marshall Dubin: 3/25/1976 (Box 295)
- Marshall Dubin: 3/25/1976 (Box 296)
- Jesse Olson: 4/17/1985 (Box 297)
- Diane Biancelli (Box 298)
- Diane Biancelli II (Box 299)
- Hilda Joguin: 6/30/1977 (Box 300)
  tape 1 only
- Bill Michaelson: 6/22/1977 (Box 301)
- Leon Davis: 1/5/1976 (Box 302)
- Irving Goffshagen: 1/16/1976 (Box 303)
- Phil Kamenkowitz I: 11/29/976, 1976 (Box 304)
- Kamenkowitz II (Box 305)
- Harry Van Arsdale: 9/7/1977 (Box 306)
- Dennis Rivera: 6/14/2006 (Box 308)
- Dennis Rivera: 5/15/2007 (Box 309)
- Dan North: 5/26/2006 (Box 310)
- Aida Garcia: 1/9/2007 (Box 311)
- George Gresham: 5/15/2007 (Box 312)
- pam Brion - 6/13/2006 (Box 313)
- Naomi Masters: 7/1/2006 (Box 314)
- Jennifer Cunningham: 6/15/2006 (Box 315)
- Rosselli - Borsas: 6/23/2007 (Box 316)
- Deborah Kirk II: 8/7/2006 (Box 317)
- Sal Rosselli, John Barsos: 6/23/2007 (Box 318)
- Jerry Brown: 7/4/2006 (Box 319)
- Jerry Brown II: 7/4/2006 (Box 320)
- George Gresham: 6/18/2008 (Box 321)
- Gay Sackman: 6/14/2006 (Box 322)
- George Gresham: 8/9/2006 (Box 323)
- George Gresham: 8/8/2006 (Box 324)
- Jan Reuther: 6/15/2006 (Box 325)
- Eddie Kay (Box 326)
- John Reid: 6/15/2006 (Box 327)
- Spencer Foreman: 6/15/2006 (Box 328)
- Peton Lazes: 8/1/2006 (Box 329)
- Bruce Potter: 2/19/2006 (Box 330)
- Andy Storm: 5/5/2006 (Box 331)